(Kripke:)Come on, they have birthday parties here.
Little kids climb this.
(Sheldon:)Little kid hominids, perhaps.
So is this your entire job?
(Sheldon:)Your parents must be so proud.
(Kripke:)Let's go, Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Coming, Kripke.
(Sheldon:)Okay, harness seems to be secure.
A small amount of incontinence just now,
but the website said that's to be expected.
(Howard:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)This isn't so bad.
It's a bit like vertical swimming.
(Kripke:)Look at you.
You're almost halfway to the top.
(Sheldon:)I am? I...
(Sheldon:)I was wrong.
(Sheldon:)It is a fear of heights.
- You all right there, Cooper?
- Not really.
I feel like an inverse tangent function
that's approaching an asymptote.
(Kripke:)- Stuck?
- What part of "inverse tangent function...